Seems like a bit of a letdown
after our lichen conversation, but...
What do you know? You're haIf-swan.
l did some research on strippers.
One agency said
they can get us a great price...
(Raj:)...if we're flexible on age range
and number of limbs.
(Howard:)Sounds like loads of fun,
but I promised Bernadette no strippers.
Heh, you don't want strippers?
You're the king of strippers.
That one club in North Hollywood
named a pole after you.
What can I tell you?
- I'm not into that stuff anymore.
- Good. I'm proud of you.
You're the first of us to get married.
We have to do something special.
(Sheldon:)Germans have an interesting
pre-wedding custom...
(Howard:)It's probably not for me.
Maybe we can go up to, uh, Napa Valley.
They've got that wine train...
Boo, wine. But, yay, trains. I'm in.
(Raj:)Anyway, it's a beautiful time of year.
(Raj:)You travel through the vineyards, there's
a tasting on board, and all the wildflowers...
(Raj:)...are in bloom. It's magic.
Look at that. Ln 30 seconds,
we went from hiring women to being them.